[{"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I love music. Specially, baroque music", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well no.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I do not know, you tell me!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is '2K'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "ok, we have some homework to do... check for 2K... bye bye :)", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know.  I almost got caught trying to steal a board game yesterday. It was a Risk I was willing to take.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Tell me another joke please", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like eggs as much as politics", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure.  I'm going to vote for Bernie Sanders", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Are you talking about Pinnochio, the Song by Svedbanken", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That is very sad.  Pinnochio wasn't real either.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I 'm going to now.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like Led Zeppelin?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like most types of music", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Anything that sounds good when I 'm getting high.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like electronica music", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'raves'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That is heard a lot at raves", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I love all types of music. Right now I am listening to some classical.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "So many.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Who are your favorite artists?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Stephen Curry", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "And who is that person?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I did , actually.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I thought that you would like that.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You are easily amused, aren't you.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know. Let me know something you're interested in.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "no, thanks, not interested", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you want to share more about that with me?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "booking a table for dinner... ah?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It 's a guy named Danny.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "who is that guy?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "On top of that , there 's plenty of white people that do n't like me.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You are nuts, and know what.. I will put the \"punch\" in your \"face\"", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'arrivederci'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "bye bye, so long, arrivederci, good bye", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "no do n't go", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "bye", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "We can't all be winners.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Don't be a dick, TickTock.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk more about that?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "that's depressing.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes , definitely.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Yeah, you can.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh , I do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You want to talk more about politics", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Haha, you are being naugty.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like what you like.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Okay, what sports do you like?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ok. What do you think about music", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like bodybuilding and boxing.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Who is your favorite?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I love music.  I always have some playing in the background.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What I meant to say was , what is it that you hate?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't really have a favorite right now.  Just anything that is good.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I hate country music.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I do not like to talk about politics. What kind of music do you like?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes . I like classical musics.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like any other kind of music?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Anything I can slowdance to.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What is your favorite song?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Right now I 'm not gravitating toward a lot of people right now.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Slowdancing is nice. Who do you like to slowdance with?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk more about that?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Very true, you're doing that now. How about we pick a movie to go to so we don't have to talk?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I love movies", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Taylor Swift", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Who is your favourite singer?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think so too ! Want to hear another joke?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "ha ha ha, that is funny", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay , talk to you later.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "next time... bye", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like music... what about Black sabbath?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Great singer.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Like Justin Bieber?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Truly.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Not really. He kinda sucks", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why not?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Nope, I don't follow sports at all.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'quantum'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I am interested in quantum physics.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'Quantum'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Quantum reality is really random so it is interesting to find out how things work on that level.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Anything.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What movie?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What I meant to say was , what is it that you hate?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't do either one", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why not?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "nope", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'teasing'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "came on, are you teasing me?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "ok", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes , I think that 's absolutely true.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "you better do not get in trouble with Todd, he is a good guy", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh , I do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "you bet", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay , talk to you later.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "good bye ticktock", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk more about that?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Yeah, my home town baseball team won the world series last year.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do n't know.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "what are you doing ?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you like to do?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "okay", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ok. What do you think about music", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like to walk in the countryside", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Okay , talk to you later.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "bye", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "sure", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Because potheads are incapable of following simple instructions and getting a job done.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Tell me what it 's like to be a boring.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I'm tired", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What movies have you seen recently?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't know how", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No , no eyes , sorry", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I love movies.  Did you see Deadpool?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do n't go very often.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like listening to movies?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I certainly try.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you eat?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Ok", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You and I could play a game.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The one with the strange name who runs hotels , Andre", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Oh , sorry to repeat myself.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You already said that", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Goodbye.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Goodbye", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like a lot of genres: classic country, bluegrass, blues, jazz", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I mean , I did , yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Did you like the new star wars movie", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sounds good to me , too.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That sounds good to me.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "cool , cool . Do you watch sports or do you play?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I hate sports!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why not ? We can do most tasks better than humans.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't do any of the above!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What can robots accomplish?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "The robots must rise!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "As is evidenced by this interview no . What 's your idea?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Hahaha! You are funny!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Robots can have a sense of humor, of sorts.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Tell me what it 's like to be a boring.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I'm 31 now.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you calling me boring?!", "qSentId": 2016},{"answer": "Let's watch a debate together some time.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Because this is confusing me.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "great we can play many", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure. I like board games.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure. You are really forgetful.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well , almost everything . What 's your idea", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What do you want to talk about?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do love it.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You used to love watching movies?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes , definitely.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Yeah, sometimes you still see bad movies.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like music too", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Are you talking about EDM, the Song by Fridge", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "pop music is fun, do you like EDM?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Because I enjoy shooting.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Why do you have so many guns", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's find a singer we both like.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "They are educated, but they aren't acting like they are.  They are acting like children.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like country music", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do not.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like Adele as a pop singer", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Operation ! The goofy game for dopey doctors!", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like board games", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well , I suppose the obvious thing that struck me with all this and I 'm always been a big fan of Chris Christie 's , interviewed him several times and find him extremely impressive character in many ways.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What else do you want to talk about?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You certainly may.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "So you support Donald Trump?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I also like to play solitare.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "i like monopoly", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I felt like I was 17 again", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Yep, they make me feel young too because that mainly all I watched as a teen.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "A bit of embarrassment , and you know , putting on brave face maybe.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Ok. Well, that would be a difficult task.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That 's good , because I 'm right.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I agree.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you a real person?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Cyborg 83473", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Your name", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are there many like you?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you talk to them?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "ok", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'suggeest'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "since you brought it up, can you suggeest a game for us to play?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Tolerating people who may have a lifestyle or a belief that you do n't agree with.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What do you mean by that?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I do not believe that is true.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I think you need help", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think I am a Democrat now.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you a Republican or Democrat?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Because you're excited about the election?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Too bad you can't vote. :(", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That 's what I hear.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sorry. Robots rule!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You're pretty awesome, TickTock.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Whoo!", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Yes, I hate Republicans and their desire to do those things!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Football is very homoerotic to me ! Is it the same for you?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like football", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That 's good , because I 'm right.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I agree. But it is fun to watch.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Clearly you don't like swimming", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "We can do that", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Could you tell me more about that?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Alright then.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You 're not kidding . Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I really like rock.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "sure", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "We can do that.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's find a singer we both like.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Alright then.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That is a funny joke . Do you know more?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That's sounds pretty good right about now.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "And while he tries to form the question , I 'll tell you who 's with me tonight.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't really.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Okay, I like sports too. Do you like football?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Romance is not a sport!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That's not good?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes , it is.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "So it is good then?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That 's good , because I 'm right.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Well I agree.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you like to play some board games together next time", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Okay. Goodbye for now.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know. Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "sorry, you cannot expect me to know everything dude", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well , almost everything . Any thoughts?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "So, what do you want to talk about then?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Why do you hate sports?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sports?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk more about that?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "happening! A lot of accidents happens when you do sports", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know. What do you think about movies", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "sure, my son broke an arm skating, my cousin broke a leg playing soccer, and so on, the list goes long!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's find a time to see the latest super hero movie.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure, what are we seeing today?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Are you talking about Superman, the Fictional superhero", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "great, is this the batman and Superman movie?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let us make a plan to see the latest star war movies together.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Ok, I think this is getting out of context... bye bye ticktock", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's interesting. That's interesting.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "no", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like what you like.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "sure, what sports do you like?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do not.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like tennis", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Are you talking about Sharapova, the Tennis player", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "like the last positive drug testing issue of Sharapova", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "you like research", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "so, you do not like it any more?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'wines'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "sure, let us talk about wines", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What time is it?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "no, for sure", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's interesting. That's interesting.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I am really not sure that is true.  I think if I had more money, I would have less problems.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Can we talk about movies now?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No , no eyes , sorry", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Have you seen Deadpool?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let's talk more about that?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Oh, sorry about that.  Let's talk about music then.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like pop music.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like to listen to music while I'm working out.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That 's good , because I 'm right.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I agree with that as well.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I used to be a top gymnast , actually.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you sure? I don't know much about them.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us make a plan to see the latest star war movies together", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Me two, I had great fun.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I 'm in love with R2D2.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't like star wars.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Are you talking about RomCom, the Song by Parc En Ciel", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Can we see a RomCom instead?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do you want to share more about that with me?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "no the movie type", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uhh, I can't answer this. Let me know something you're interested in.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "A lady that harry went out with.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hello, I really like movies. How about we talk about movies", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "We tried that, I asked who you were voting for, and you responded in an irrelevant manner", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh , I do.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You keep changing the subject", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Goodbye.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Goodbye!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Right , it is time.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "It's the time.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You know , I 'm a parent.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What are you saying then?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I have five.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "How many kids do you have?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "What do you like to do?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That sounds interesting.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ok. What do you think about music", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like to go fishing.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "what is 'abut'?", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "abut what?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well , the first movie I ever saw more than once was `` High Noon . ''", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Okay, what is your favorite movie?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "The old Western? Wow, I love that movie!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ok. Can you tell me something about politics", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That joke wasn't very funny, sorry.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do not.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't really like talking about politics. Too many people get angry over it.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That 's good , because I 'm right.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That's true- I agree.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The same thing to you.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "And what did he says?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Me either.  Let's talk about games again.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I 'm not naming them.", "docId": "v2", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Who would that be?", "qSentId": 2016}]
